- Once there was
a boy named James,
my grandson,
a child who learned the weight
of goodbye far too young.
After his parents died,
he came to live with me
in a house of old wood
and ticking clocks.
A house full of memory.
Then death is a greedy visitor.
It never comes just once.
It returned
and it took his
very best friend.
I watched the boy's heart break.
So then I made a vow.
You will never
lose anyone again.
I worked.
I spent more and more
time in the basement,
a place forbidden to James.
Days turned to weeks
creating something,
something just for him.
Something which will
never say goodbye.
never belong to death.
Pinocchio.
Not today. Thanks.
- Oh gosh, no, not again.
No. Come on.
This joke is so old it
should be in a nursing home.
- Um, Bye James.
- How's he holding up?
- Oh, he had
a moment earlier,
but I think he'll be okay.
- And you?
- I'm good as can be.
Yeah, thanks.
Bye.
- Thanks for keeping
an eye on him lately.
- Zach, wait up.
- Grab your coat, kiddo.
Bit of fresh air
will do us good.
Now come on.
It's always hard losing
someone you love.
Your mother, now
your best friend.
- Do you ever worry, Granddad,
about what happens after?
Like, when we die.
- All I worry about is you.
- I just, I wish
Zach was still here.
It doesn't feel
the same anymore.
- Well, maybe he is.
I believe what makes you, you,
sticks around after and
moves into what surrounds us.
- Yeah, Dudley told me
that stuff's rubbish.
- I've seen Dudley pick
his nose and eat it too.
Look up.
What do you see?
- Um, loads of stars.
- "There are more things in
heaven and earth, Horatio,
"than are dreamt of
in your philosophy."
It means life is full of
endless possibilities.
- Granddad, are you okay?
Are you okay? Do you want me to-
- I'm fine. Don't worry.
- You sure?
- Mm.
Fine.
We should get home soon.
I have something very
exciting to show you tomorrow.
You sure there's nothing
else you remember?
James?
- Who are you talking to?
- Come down.
There's someone here
I want you to meet.
- Someone?
- Come, come.
- Is that what I saw upstairs?
- That'll be him.
- Where is he?
- In there.
He's shy, I think.
Come on out.
I want you to meet someone.
He's the boy I've been
telling you about.
Yes, him.
You're the first
person he's seen
other than me.
I think he wants
to be your friend.
- Stop! Go away!
Please stop!
- James, stop!
Listen to me, James.
- What the fuck was that?
- Calm down and
watch your language-
- No, no, no, no!
What was that? That
thing down there?
What? What is it?
- It's not a thing.
It's a who, James.
It's alive.
Things aren't always
what they seem,
life is not-
- What were you talking about?
- I know it's hard to believe,
but trust me in time, this
is all gonna make sense.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I just thought you
could use a friend.
I know he could.
- A friend?
With, with that thing?
- This could be
good for the both of you.
- How long has he
been down there?
- That's all
he's ever really known.
Why don't you say hello?
- James.
- I'm Pinocchio.
Are we friends?
- Maybe. We'll see.
- James,
you can tell nobody about this.
Understood?
Good boy.
- You're not gonna get
my ship, Captain James.
- Oh, I'm gonna make
you walk the plank.
Okay. You got it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Your move.
- Is that me?
- Yeah.
Now.
- Dude.
What the fuck is that?
- Nothing. Nothing.
It's just a doll Granddad made.
This one's biology.
- What is bilology?
- It's like why boys are
made different from you.
Organs and stuff.
- Wow.
What else makes us different?
- Teeth, eyes, hair, skin.
I mean, there's lots of things.
- I wanna be just like you.
- No, trust me.
You don't.
You're way cooler than me.
- What's this?
- Oh.
Uh...
- As the herd
follows the sea's plains,
danger lies in wait.
But in the presence
of a predator,
the herd will
protect one another.
- The herd will protect.
You are my herd.
- However,
sometimes the greatest danger
comes from within the group.
- James.
Why?
- You can't.
- I want to be with James.
- He's going to school tomorrow.
People won't react well.
- Because I don't have a penis?
- No, I don't know
what to say to that.
The world isn't ready for you.
Not yet.
- Like 100 kg.
- Rubbish, mate.
- Pure muscle, it's just hidden.
Just need to do, like, a diet.
- Need some help with that?
- You can do that?
- I could help you
lose five pounds, easy.
- How?
- I just cut off a right arm.
- Ah!
- Ah! Fuck!
Ouch, my head.
- Child, come closer.
My splinters hurt.
- You talk?
- Who else would tell
the truth he hides?
- What are you?
- I am your Wood Mother.
Geppetto may have
carved our bodies,
but I will shape your mind.
- Are you stuck there?
- As are you.
- I'm not stuck.
- The strings may be invisible,
but you are still his puppet.
- I'm no puppet.
I'm just like James.
I'm a real boy.
- Your
nose betrays you.
The creator says you are real.
He doesn't look
at you like James.
You want his arms to
hold you, not hide you,
then come closer
and I'll whisper how to be real.
You need skin,
blood, teeth, hair.
Take them, wear them.
- Ew, that's disgusting.
I'm not doing that.
- Then stay caged,
little puppet,
whilst James walks in sunlight.
Unless I'm wrong.
Prove it.
- Wow.
- Pinocchio?
Oh, there you are.
- Who are these?
- Oh, they're my best mates.
- Best mates?
- Yeah.
It's like a friend forever.
Someone you protect
and you never break a
promise to and stuff.
- Are we best mates?
- Put out your hand.
We've got to do this to
make it official first.
A super secret handshake.
Now first we slap our
fist both sides, like,
and then...
That's, that's right.
Good guess.
- Are you going again tomorrow?
- Yeah.
And you're coming with me.
But you've gotta make one
of those promises first.
No matter what, no
one can see you move.
Just be like a doll, yeah?
- Easy.
- Why are
you all tied up?
- Father
says it's to protect me.
- Oh, I've gotta meet Dudley.
Oh, here you go.
- Ouch.
- Oh, you're heavy.
- No, I'm not.
- Dentist
after school, James.
- See you later, Granddad!
- See you, kiddo.
- Whoa, this is amazing.
Wow.
- That's Trey and
that's where he lives.
He's a proper asshole.
- Asshole.
Hey James.
What's an asshole?
- Uh, I'll explain another time.
- Ah.
Oh.
So,
is he an ass or
the hole of an ass?
- Hey!
- So everyone,
how do we determine
what makes someone bad?
- Bad?
- Each of you
have an internal conscience,
like a compass
guiding you towards what
you believe is right.
- Just trying to make sure
fucking obliterated to bits.
Hey, let's go, dick weed.
- One second.
I can't take you in there.
Just stay here and
don't mess anything up.
- James, are you
talking to your bag?
- Coming.
Yeah, it's gonna be out.
- Strange.
- Have his arm ripped off.
- Up, down.
Up, down.
Don't worry, James.
I won't let anyone see me.
Best friend handshake, yeah.
Oh no.
Are you okay?
Oh my God. Watch out.
Jesus. I've gotta go.
Promise you won't
tell anyone about me.
What are they for?
- Ages ago we used to
play pretend superheroes.
Dudley wanted to be that guy.
This one, ugly one is Dudley.
- Wow, that looks just like him.
- Yeah, I know.
It means I could just
stop him and he's-
Shit.
Don't move.
- Okay.
- Yo, bro, you've been
very hard to find today.
Playing with your
little dolls again?
- They aren't dolls.
- He's gotten himself a
bigger one, hasn't he?
Yeah.
Hey, hey.
- No, no, no.
- Get off me!
- Your granddad's
rich as fuck anyway,
with all that old money.
Think of this as tax.
- No wonder Mia dumped you.
- Oh.
- Listen, the only
reason why she likes you,
because you are an
even bigger loser
than your dead ass friend.
- Oh!
- Hold him while I fuck
this whole shit up.
- What the fuck are you doing?
No!
God, I fucking hate you!
I fucking hate you!
Don't touch him! Get off me!
- You tell anyone
about this, dickhead,
I'll kill you.
- What the fuck, Trey?
- The kid started it.
- Hey, you need
to fucking leave.
All of you!
James.
They're pretty bad guys, right?
- The worst.
I wish they were all dead.
Thanks Mia.
- Come here.
Hey, who's this little fella?
- Oh, that's Pinocchio.
He's special.
- Well, how about I go find
Dudley and you can show us?
- What do you
mean you went to the gym?
- Apparently it has to
be in this secret area.
- James, what? Whoa!
What is that?
Oh, your granddad's made a
proper freaky one this time.
Oh, look at that nose.
- Okay guys, there is
something wanted to show you.
Promise it stays between us.
- Yeah, sure. Promise.
- Yeah, sure.
- Pinocchio, it's
okay. They can see.
Pinocchio.
- No fucking way!
Okay, this is
officially the coolest
and creepiest thing
I've ever seen.
How's he doing that?
- Uh...
- Come on, man. What is it?
- Is this some like,
AI thing, James?
- Yeah, exactly.
Uh, the wires are hidden in
the brain chip in his head.
- Brain chip?
- The CPU or whatever.
No matter what,
my granddad can never
ever find out I have him.
It cost like, one
million pounds.
Crap. Sorry guys, gotta go.
I'm late for my dentist.
- Mate, mate.
Mate, this ain't over!
I'm coming straight
'round after!
- It's really gonna
hurt, isn't it?
Can we use some of that, um?
Can we use some of that
stuff to put me to sleep?
- We can't.
Just be brave, alright?
- Are you sure?
- It'll be over
before you know it
and you'll have perfect
teeth just like mine.
Come on. Open wide.
All done.
- Ah.
- That will really help.
Shouldn't feel anything now.
- So, how
are you feeling James?
- Ah, it hurts like hell.
- Ah, you'll
be fine by tomorrow.
- Are you okay?
Help me! Ah!
Oh no.
James?
- Hello, hello?
- Is this the
Geppetto residence?
- Who's this?
- I'm calling
from St. Mary's Hospital.
Your grandchild's
been in an accident.
- You've got a visitor.
How's he getting on?
- Yeah, no, he's fine.
Just superficial wounds.
But he does have signs
of mild concussion.
But I think with a little
bit of sleep he'll be okay.
- What happened?
- Drunk driver.
And the same one as last year.
That reminds me, I need
to go and check on him
'cause he's in pretty bad shape.
Wish me luck.
- Good luck.
Oh James, please don't die.
You're my best friend.
And best friends,
best friends,
best friends protect each other.
Yeah.
- You're just seeing
things, Larry.
It's all in your head.
- Dr.
Robin, there you are.
Whoo!
Oh no.
Fuckity fuck.
Ew.
Where have you gone?
- The paralysis is
temporary, so try not to worry.
I'm gonna get
something for the pain.
Found you.
There you are.
- Hello.
You're the bad man.
You're pure evil.
It's all your fault.
James is my friend.
He's my best friend.
I'm going to take care of him.
So I need to make to you dead.
- No, no.
- Silence will get you nowhere.
The herd will protect
one another, bad man.
- Oh!
- And your reign
of terror is over.
- Oh, ah!
- You deserve to be made dead.
- Ah!
- So Mr. Drunk,
off to hell you go!
Take this!
This is what happens
to bad people!
This is for James!
Like it's raining.
♪ Rain, rain, go away ♪
♪ Come again another day ♪
The world won't miss
someone like you.
Stop complaining.
Why won't you just die?
Organs and stuff.
Bilology.
I can use this.
I'm going to be a real boy.
I'm going to be just like James.
It's cool.
You have so much of this stuff.
Yes, yes! This so fun!
So much of this stuff.
Wow.
James is safe.
Your reign of terror is over.
For James!
Uh-oh.
- It was right
after the dentist.
- He just came out of nowhere?
- Yeah.
Oh!
- I'll call the nurse.
- No, no, no.
It seems to have
calmed down now.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah,
I should be fine.
- You alright, James?
We got your scans back
and you are good to go.
- Already?
- Yeah.
No, he's absolutely fine.
Just lots of rest. Okay?
- Thanks.
- Let's get you home, kiddo.
I'll grab your bag.
- Wait, wait, I'll grab my bag.
- Okay.
You're being very strange.
- Oh, did you see him?
- But he was bad.
- Look who's come to see you.
- James, your granddad told us.
- James!
- All right, kiddos.
I'm heading out to
get pizzas in a bit.
So no filling up on crap.
- Thanks Granddad.
- Yeah, your AI thing.
- Oh shit!
Let's go start that thing!
- Reckon you could be
a bit louder, Dudley?
Remember, secret.
- Ugh! What kind of
AI doll leaks shit?
- I'm always on.
- Are you leaking?
- They're my organs.
They're making me real.
- Ugh! What the hell?
James, mate, why is it leaking?
Ugh.
- I'll explain later, just,
just get it back before
Granddad returns.
- James.
- Come on, Dudley.
Come on.
Dudley, quick.
Bring him over.
Come on, man.
- I need to stay
and protect you.
- You can't.
Granddad can't know.
This is our secret, remember?
- But you're in danger.
- James, what's all this?
Yes, Lord James.
- Let go of me!
Filthy boy! Don't you dare!
I wanna go home! Ah!
- No, Pinocchio, stop!
- Dudley one, Pinocchio nil.
- James, please.
- I'm sorry.
When Granddad's
gone, I'll come back.
Promise.
- Hurry up, come on.
- Coming.
- Oh, we can play the
synchronized protector.
- Everything all right?
- I'll find you in a minute.
Uh, sick.
- You feel sick?
- No, like a good sick.
Like I feel good. Yeah.
- Right.
You remember what we
spoke about, right?
- Yeah.
I know, Granddad.
- Alright, kiddo.
Take it easy on yourself.
- Yeah.
- Stupid
bloody rope! Ah!
- Oh, there you are,
little splinter.
Come closer.
Tell your old Wood
Mother what rots you.
- They're hiding me
because I'm different, but,
but James is in danger.
- Danger? That child?
From who?
- Lots of bad people.
One almost killed him.
So, so I had to make him dead.
- My clever, clever boy.
Protecting your brother.
That is real love.
- Was that bad?
- Bad? Killing him?
Of course not.
You were just protecting him.
And that was only the beginning.
You know what to do with
the other bad people now.
Yes?
- Get rid of them too?
- Precisely!
One by one
until they're all gone.
Then James will be safe.
And remember,
if you want to be truly real,
take what they have.
Piece by piece
to make yourself whole.
- Woo-hoo!
Whoa!
- Yes, in here.
This will work.
- And why are we in
this dusty old place?
- Because I think Geppetto
is hiding something
and I want to know
what's on these tapes.
- I was right.
My belief that the
soul, life, energy,
whatever you want to call it,
does indeed remain after
death and can be harnessed.
This could lead to a kind of
rebirth that allows us to,
to cheat death.
I heard this strange wailing,
but just come, watch.
- What is that?
- After shaping it
into moving forward,
it's progressing faster
and with help will
gain motor function.
It's learning incredibly fast.
My work has taken a turn.
The subject is dangerous.
Born evil.
It's developed an
obsession to be human
and escape these walls.
I need to reset.
- James, did you know
about any of this?
- Why can't it just make noise?
Why does it gotta make you shit?
Look at that.
- Yeah, play this one.
It was two days ago.
- So far no experiment
has recalled
one memory from its prior life,
till then I can't be confident
it is indeed a form of rebirth.
My next experiment, Pinocchio,
will be exposed to
external stimuli
to help evoke those memories.
Tonight he meets my grandson.
- Now where are you?
Oh, get off! What the hell?
Who are you?
- Name's Cricket.
Your Wood Mother sent me
to keep you on the right
path and obey the grownups.
- To help James?
- That's right.
The world's full of
rot you need to stop,
like whoever is in that room.
- Oh my God.
- And remember, piece by piece,
we'll take what's left.
Everything you need to be real.
- Thanks Cricket.
Let's do this
for James.
- Let's make that bitch choke.
Look.
She's collecting them.
- That horrible woman.
Open wide.
- Take this!
- Nasty tooth pulling bitch!
You won't hurt James again.
For James.
I saw what you did to James.
You can't hide behind
those masks any longer.
This will help.
You shouldn't feel a thing.
- Yeah, smash that grin
off her shitty face.
Make sure she says cheese.
- Thanks Cricket.
Just be brave.
It'll be over
before you know it.
Never hurt James again,
you horrible lady!
- Good lad.
Now let's give you a smile.
- Shh, these are mine now.
Hey, now I have
the perfect smile,
just like you.
James.
I can't wait to
show James.
- Pinocchio?
- Oh my God.
I bet that creepy ass thing's
in this room somewhere.
- Why didn't you tell us, James?
- You said
it was a robot.
- Oh no, he's missing.
Call, call my phone.
- What? Why?
- Quick, just do it.
Pinocchio?
- James!
- Does he have teeth?
- What are you doing?
- I'm stopping all
the bad people!
- You're stopping them how?
- Everyone keeps hurting you,
so I have to protect you.
Look.
- Holy fuck!
- No, no, no, Pinocchio.
That's not what I meant.
- Oh.
- What?
- Oh, he's muted now.
No more. No more.
- More?
Oh, kill more!
- Oh fuck.
- Oh my God.
- Good job, Dudley.
- Wait, come back!
I need to kill you!
- No, Pinocchio, stop.
- Come back!
Come back here with that lady!
- Pinocchio, that's not-
- Come on, guys.
We've gotta go stop him.
That's the church
behind my dentist.
- James? Mia?
Shit!
Pinocchio!
- Found you, asshole.
- James, answer your phone now!
Where have you taken him?
- One day you're gonna
have to come around,
you know what I'm saying?
- No, stop it.
- Stop being so lame, come on.
- Annoying.
- Yo.
- Asshole.
- Wait, wait!
- Nasty boy.
- Logan!
It's too cold.
Logan!
- Oh no, you don't!
- Swim, swim, swim,
little guppy.
- I didn't know they
keep whales in here.
Here I come, naughty girl!
Swim, swim, stupid lady.
I'll fucking kill you, bitch!
This nasty bully.
Cricket! Cricket, where are you?
Ah!
- I'm
coming. I'm coming.
I'm three inches tall.
Cut me some slack.
- Stop squiggling!
I need to send you to hell!
- Pay attention, Pinocch.
Time for a science lesson.
Zap, zap, motherfucker!
- Hi Logan.
Come on, you know it's me.
- The eyes. The eyes.
Not the tongue.
The eyes are what you need.
- Give me that!
Yeah!
- Pop 'em in, kid.
One more step to
being just like James.
- Teeth.
Eyes.
Lots of things.
- Pinocchio?
Where the hell is he?
Oh fuck!
Oh, fucking hell.
- Mia, call the police.
- And tell them what, Dudley?
That a homicidal
doll is on the loose?
- He's not a
homicidal doll, okay?
He's just, he's
trying to protect me.
- Sure, James.
- He, he's a killer.
I mean, look, he's
literally killing.
He's literally killing.
- James.
- It's all my,
it's all my fault!
- James, is there anyone
that you can think of
that he might target next?
- Oh fuck! Oh shit!
Trey!
- Trey? Dudley!
- Ooh la la.
She cut her penis off.
What the hell?
- Wait, what?
She's getting dressed already?
Let me show you how
it's done, Pinocch.
Let's go, you dirty bitch.
You stupid skank.
Give me that!
- What
are you doing?
- This hair,
it's gonna make you real!
That hair isn't yours to keep.
- Oh, oh! My nose!
Get off it! Please
get off my nose!
Get off it now! Get off it!
Ow! Ow!
Come back!
- Come on, kid.
Real boys don't quit.
- Come back!
- Amanda?
- This is my hair!
Stop screaming!
It's mine!
- What the fuck?
- Oh.
No, you? You're
James' fucking doll.
- Yeah, 'tis me.
- No! Fuck this!
- Look at me. It's real.
- No, get the fuck away from me.
- I'm not a doll, Trey.
And I'm not a puppet.
- Oh fuck!
- You won't take
dreams away from me.
- Help!
- You can't hurt James anymore.
It's too late to lie now.
You're my best friend.
You're such a nice guy.
I don't want to kill you.
- Cricket, one.
Bald skank, zero.
- We're at least
10 minutes away.
What if he?
- Oh shit!
Oh, shit, shit, shit.
Your crazy granddad's
calling, James.
- Dudley, what the hell?
Why'd you answer?
- Hey.
- Hey, hey Granddad.
- Where are you?
- Yeah, we just,
we just had to stop off
at Mia's really quick.
Oh, we just had to-
- Mia! Mia!
Left! Left!
Trey's is that way.
- I know where
my ex-boyfriend lives.
- Dudley!
- Gimme the phone. Go.
I know what to do.
Yeah, so.
- You hung up?
- Yeah, now he's definitely
not gonna suspect anything.
Is he?
- Little shit.
- I remember when you were
just a little splinter.
Now, beautiful.
Complete.
Finally
a real boy.
One hell of a glow up, kid.
- I'm gorgeous.
♪ Oh, you beautiful doll ♪
♪ You great big beautiful doll ♪
♪ Let me put my
arms around you ♪
♪ I could never
live without you ♪
♪ Oh, you beautiful doll ♪
♪ You great big beautiful doll ♪
♪ If you ever leave me
how my heart will ache ♪
♪ I wanna hug you,
but I need a break ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- Hmm, what do you think?
This hat suit me, Pinocch?
- Look, Father,
I made a puppet too.
- Is that your granddad's car?
- Oh yeah.
There he goes.
- James.
- Off to wreck more lives.
- Pinocchio.
Quick, Mia. Go after him.
- They're both killers.
Oh!
- They were going to hurt James.
But why?
Why, that nasty, lying bitch.
You lied to me.
Why did you lie to me?
- Messed up, haven't
you, little splinter?
- This is all your fault.
- You carved this path yourself.
- You got me to do
those bad things.
I'm not gonna let
you trick me anymore.
- Greedy.
Dissatisfied with what you are.
I should be where you are!
Look at me when I'm speaking!
- You've made everyone hate me.
- Because you're bad, Pinocchio.
Bad as the ones you butchered.
- We raised you to be
a good boy, Pinocch.
- Oh, get off me,
Cricket!
There you are!
- Don't you dare!
- Leave him alone!
- No! You dumb bitch!
Nasty Wood Mother!
I'll teach you,
you stupid asshole!
Wrinkly shit!
- There's something
I need to show you.
You want to be real
because of your past.
Come with me.
- What
is this place?
- It's
where you were created.
- Oh my God.
- It feeds through the roots,
growing as it siphons
their life force
infusing itself into the wood.
The same wood I then harvest.
That's right.
You are the mere existence.
When their life
ended, yours began.
- Where did they come from?
- Once I realized I
could harvest it, I
began to study them.
Trying to understand
how they worked,
trying to perfect the process.
There were many failures.
- It's moving.
- One of which was
particularly dangerous.
So I had to keep it locked away.
But then you came along,
my perfect creation.
You had so much potential.
- Potential?
For what?
- To prove that I was right.
That we could be reborn.
That we can master death.
But ultimately you're as much
a failure as the rest of them.
- Oh.
- Your granddad
is a killer, James.
What could we do
against a killer?
- You're absolutely sure?
- Yes.
You saw what he did
to that other doll.
He doesn't deserve to die, okay?
- James, like, maybe
it's better if he does.
- I agree. Dudley's right.
- He was doing it to protect me!
- But your granddad
is a murderer, James.
- Whatever, stay here then.
- Stop.
Not listening at all, are you?
- It's strange.
Both of us wanting to
be like each other.
- Who did I come from?
- A young boy.
A dear friend of James'.
- Zach?
- Pinocchio came from
Zach?
- What the hell?
- I'd hoped Zach and
James' friendship
would show that
death isn't the end.
- That's it.
This is just getting
worse and worse.
I'm getting out of this place.
Your granddad is
an absolute freak.
- But I don't want to die.
- Your death is
what's best for James.
- No.
- He's gone
mental and he has to die.
- Fucking kid.
- I, I can't listen to him.
We need to save him.
- James, help me please!
- Pinocchio?
- James, Mia,
Father's gone crazy.
- I know. I don't
want you to die.
Okay? You're in danger.
- James! Mia!
Help me!
Oh!
- Oh fuck!
- You bitch.
- Dudley, no!
- He locked the door.
- Untie me quick.
- Now!
- I know somewhere we can hide.
- No, no, no, no.
- Down there.
- We have to go. Now.
- James!
They have to die!
- Wait for me!
- I have no choice.
- Guys! Guys!
- Hide! Come on!
- You killed Dudley!
I fucking hate you!
- Shh, shh, shh, shh.
It's okay. I can bring
Dudley back, boy.
I can bring Dudley back and
I'll bring Mia back too.
James, James, this
was all for you, boy.
- No it wasn't. No it wasn't.
No it wasn't. No it wasn't.
- You disobeyed me, James.
Do you think those friends
wouldn't say anything?
They're children!
- You're a monster!
- Let me in.
Let me in, James.
- No.
- Let me in.
- No! I fucking hate you!
- Let me in!
Open the fucking door!
Now you're ruining everything!
Get out of the way, boy.
Get away from the
fucking door, kid!
Mia!
Come out.
Come on, boys and girls.
I'm on the cusp of
something great.
Something bigger than you both.
You know I can't let you win.
No way.
Dr. Gammon showed me how
to bring you all back.
You ruined everything.
It's time to die.
You can all be my puppets!
- Leave them alone.
- What the fuck?
- You forget yourself.
I made you.
- I'm not your puppet anymore.
- Yes you are.
Without me you're
just a piece of wood.
- No! I'm more than that.
- A puppet needs a master.
And I'm the only one
that can make you real.
Make you like James.
- I don't wanna be
like James anymore.
I just wanna be me.
- And you're always
gonna be hollow inside.
Incomplete, splintered,
and cracked.
- Pinocchio, don't listen.
- You, you can't
control me anymore.
- I gave you life!
I'm not only your
father, Pinocchio,
I'm your God!
And your God 'til I fucking die!
- Fuck you!
- Goodbye.
God.
- Holy fuck.
- Whoa!
- Ah!
- James, we need to go.
- Come on!
- James, are we still friends?
Am I bad?
- You were just confused.
Just don't do it again, okay?
- I'm such a rascal, aren't I?
- Yeah, besides, I mean they
were all assholes anyway.
Oh, except my dentist.
I'm gonna need a new dentist.
- I'll get them too.
You won't tell people
about me, will you?
- No lie.
- Good. Me too.
- Come on. Let's go.
- I'll catch up.
Goodbye Father.
You made me. You can't
control me anymore.
James is mine.
- You Pinocchio!
- I didn't enjoy having to
kill them people, you know.
- That, that bloody kid.
I might be small, but I
have big plans for this one.
From roots come resurrection.
I'll bring you back, my master.
- This is behind the scenes.
And action.
Go on, go on, go on.
Oh!
And roll camera.
- What's this?
- High five?
- High five.
- Yeah.
- How's she doing?
- It's Kelly's stunt double.
Yep.
And action on the coffin.
Action!
Roll sound.
- Open your mouth.
- Action.
Okay, camera set.
Here we go.
- It's taping too fast.
In three, two, one, bang!
And sparks.
What you doing today, Vince?
- Well, just a whole-
- Relax.
- Yeah, I think
that's great, guys.
Well done.
Yeah, as you go in,
you then bring the foot.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Maybe could
someone hold the head?
Would that help? I don't know.
- I think you see the head.
- Hang on, wait a minute.
- Look at the arm.
- Chopped off.
- Oh fuck, my arm! Help!
Action.
Maybe he's like a spy.
He's looking around.
Like that, pointing it.
And three.
- Good luck.
- I'm done.
- So you okay? Ready?
- Okay.
Okay, drop.
Professional film crew.